<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Review on Die! Boredom! Die!</title>
    <link>https://dieboredomdie.co.uk/tags/review/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Review on Die! Boredom! Die!</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 25 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://dieboredomdie.co.uk/tags/review/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Dobble Review</title>
      <link>https://dieboredomdie.co.uk/2018/06/25/dobble-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dieboredomdie.co.uk/2018/06/25/dobble-review/</guid>
      <description>Sometimes you want to sit down and spend a few hours churning through a single tabletop campaign and sometimes you just want some frantic fun. The first &amp;ldquo;big&amp;rdquo; game I bought was Eldritch Horror, I was still a bit wet behind the ears when it came to tabletop gaming and I wanted something a bit meaty to sink my teeth into. I remember reading and re-reading the rule book and spending a good hour getting setup only to sit down to play but feeling like a I needed a break.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lightseekers Review</title>
      <link>https://dieboredomdie.co.uk/2018/06/07/lightseekers-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dieboredomdie.co.uk/2018/06/07/lightseekers-review/</guid>
      <description>At the start of the year D!B!D! dipped our hairy little toes in the world of Magic the Gathering. We bought Ollie 2 of the Planeswalker Decks because, let’s be honest here, we are 3 years into this whole tabletop gaming thing and we had yet to actually try any of the popular trading card games. Well actually that’s not 100% true Ollie and Nate did both go through a phase of collecting both Pokemon and Yu-Gi-Oh!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Survive Escape from Atlantis Review</title>
      <link>https://dieboredomdie.co.uk/2018/05/18/survive-escape-from-atlantis-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dieboredomdie.co.uk/2018/05/18/survive-escape-from-atlantis-review/</guid>
      <description>Survive: Escape from Atlantis is like playing Forbidden Island except you discover you&amp;rsquo;re playing Carcassonne but you&amp;rsquo;re playing it in reverse for some reason and someone decided to throw their copy of Get Bit into the mix.
Survive: Escape from Atlantis is nearly as old as me.
Survive: Escape from Atlanta is a not a Walking Dead themed version of this game but it wouldn&amp;rsquo;t surprise me if it eventually became one - you know what these crazy brands are like.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>