<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Boardgame on Die! Boredom! Die!</title>
    <link>https://dieboredomdie.co.uk/tags/boardgame/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Boardgame on Die! Boredom! Die!</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://dieboredomdie.co.uk/tags/boardgame/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Villagers - Final Hours on Kickstarter</title>
      <link>https://dieboredomdie.co.uk/2018/06/12/villagers-final-hours/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dieboredomdie.co.uk/2018/06/12/villagers-final-hours/</guid>
      <description>Villagers, a euro card drafting game, has entered its final hours of its hugely successful Kickstarter campaign and so far is just over 5000% funded - yep that is not a typo five thousand percent. So it seems I&amp;rsquo;m not the only person excited for this one.
The goal in Villagers is to rebuild your village after the Black Death has taken the lives of many people. The player who has the most prosperous village by the end is the winner.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lightseekers Review</title>
      <link>https://dieboredomdie.co.uk/2018/06/07/lightseekers-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dieboredomdie.co.uk/2018/06/07/lightseekers-review/</guid>
      <description>At the start of the year D!B!D! dipped our hairy little toes in the world of Magic the Gathering. We bought Ollie 2 of the Planeswalker Decks because, let’s be honest here, we are 3 years into this whole tabletop gaming thing and we had yet to actually try any of the popular trading card games. Well actually that’s not 100% true Ollie and Nate did both go through a phase of collecting both Pokemon and Yu-Gi-Oh!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Survive Escape from Atlantis Review</title>
      <link>https://dieboredomdie.co.uk/2018/05/18/survive-escape-from-atlantis-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dieboredomdie.co.uk/2018/05/18/survive-escape-from-atlantis-review/</guid>
      <description>Survive: Escape from Atlantis is like playing Forbidden Island except you discover you&amp;rsquo;re playing Carcassonne but you&amp;rsquo;re playing it in reverse for some reason and someone decided to throw their copy of Get Bit into the mix.
Survive: Escape from Atlantis is nearly as old as me.
Survive: Escape from Atlanta is a not a Walking Dead themed version of this game but it wouldn&amp;rsquo;t surprise me if it eventually became one - you know what these crazy brands are like.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>