<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Die! Boredom! Die!</title>
    <link>https://dieboredomdie.co.uk/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Die! Boredom! Die!</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://dieboredomdie.co.uk/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Foreign Food Friday Week #1</title>
      <link>https://dieboredomdie.co.uk/2018/06/19/foreign-food-friday-week-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dieboredomdie.co.uk/2018/06/19/foreign-food-friday-week-1/</guid>
      <description>A post about meal planning! How exciting! I’m kidding around… I am only posting about ONE night of the week… Foreign Food Friday (yes I’m all about alliteration when it comes to a themed meal plan night!). I started this mainly because I was getting so insanely bored with the weekly meal planning and drudgery of grocery shopping. Now we have shaken things up with Meat Monday (meatless wasn’t fun), Taco Tuesday, Whatever Wednesday (we need to eat quick because Wednesday is a busy evening), Tried and Tested Thursday, Foreign Food Friday, Seafood Saturday and Slow Cook Sunday.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Villagers - Final Hours on Kickstarter</title>
      <link>https://dieboredomdie.co.uk/2018/06/12/villagers-final-hours/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dieboredomdie.co.uk/2018/06/12/villagers-final-hours/</guid>
      <description>Villagers, a euro card drafting game, has entered its final hours of its hugely successful Kickstarter campaign and so far is just over 5000% funded - yep that is not a typo five thousand percent. So it seems I&amp;rsquo;m not the only person excited for this one.
The goal in Villagers is to rebuild your village after the Black Death has taken the lives of many people. The player who has the most prosperous village by the end is the winner.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lightseekers Review</title>
      <link>https://dieboredomdie.co.uk/2018/06/07/lightseekers-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dieboredomdie.co.uk/2018/06/07/lightseekers-review/</guid>
      <description>At the start of the year D!B!D! dipped our hairy little toes in the world of Magic the Gathering. We bought Ollie 2 of the Planeswalker Decks because, let’s be honest here, we are 3 years into this whole tabletop gaming thing and we had yet to actually try any of the popular trading card games. Well actually that’s not 100% true Ollie and Nate did both go through a phase of collecting both Pokemon and Yu-Gi-Oh!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Slowquest: The Art of Bodie Hartley</title>
      <link>https://dieboredomdie.co.uk/2018/06/03/slowquest-the-art-of-bodie-hartley/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dieboredomdie.co.uk/2018/06/03/slowquest-the-art-of-bodie-hartley/</guid>
      <description>Art - I&amp;rsquo;m far from an aesthete, I couldn&amp;rsquo;t tell you what colour puce is without having to look it up for the 100th time and to be honest I didn&amp;rsquo;t even know what &amp;ldquo;aesthete&amp;rdquo; meant until I looked that up. I also couldn&amp;rsquo;t tell you why that picture of a lemon floating on a sea of magnets was a scathing indictment on the 1990&amp;rsquo;s political climate in Manila - and to be entirely honest I can&amp;rsquo;t even tell you if that’s a real work of art or something I just made up - it&amp;rsquo;s been a long day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Survive Escape from Atlantis Review</title>
      <link>https://dieboredomdie.co.uk/2018/05/18/survive-escape-from-atlantis-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dieboredomdie.co.uk/2018/05/18/survive-escape-from-atlantis-review/</guid>
      <description>Survive: Escape from Atlantis is like playing Forbidden Island except you discover you&amp;rsquo;re playing Carcassonne but you&amp;rsquo;re playing it in reverse for some reason and someone decided to throw their copy of Get Bit into the mix.
Survive: Escape from Atlantis is nearly as old as me.
Survive: Escape from Atlanta is a not a Walking Dead themed version of this game but it wouldn&amp;rsquo;t surprise me if it eventually became one - you know what these crazy brands are like.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>